Wuthering
Heights
Wow, what's that?
Wuthering
Heights
A poster for the Drama Club.
Fujigaya's 54th School Play by the High School Drama Club
Nice, isn't it?
Wuthering
Heights
Fujigaya's 54th School Play by the High School Drama Club
Wuthering
Heights
Isn't it a little too powerful?
No way. It's so cool.
What are your thoughts on this, Miss Catherine?
Sugimoto's one thing, but I didn't expect to be depicted so beautifully as well...
There you have it. A word
from the actress in the poster.
But you really are beautiful, Kawasaki.
Oh, stop that.
I wonder if I can take it home when the show is over.
I wanna hang it up in my room.
Maybe it's a little low.
Yeah...
Tape.
Oh, the rehearsal is going to start.
Let's finish this quickly.
I'm glad that you're here
That's what I think about the most
I know that you're here
I'm sorry for the way I am
I couldn't tell you that yesterday
Whenever you smile
Whenever you're in tears
I'll always be there to support you
When you reach someone's heart
It will turn into a bouquet of flowers
Did you see that crazy poster?
Yes, I think it's wonderful.
You really think so?
Sugimoto!
Did you like the poster?
Yeah, I feel bad that you put so much work into it.
Oh no, I wanted to do more...
Hmm?
U-Um...
Break a leg on stage.
Thank you.
I talked to her!
What did you talk about?
I'm not telling!
Hey, not fair!
You're...
You're liked by everyone, aren't you?
What? Are you jealous?
Maybe I am.
Fumi?
Darn, no good.
I told you we have to get closer.
I find myself doubting her.
Huh?
I wonder if she has someone else she likes.
That's all I've been able to think about since then.
It gets in the way of our conversations when I'm talking to her.
Well, I'm not the best person to ask about this,
but they say that people get anxious
when they have feelings for someone...
Couldn't it be something like that?
Maybe you're right...
Okudaira.
Oh, lkumi.
What kind of juice do you want?
Juice?
I'm asking everyone.
The club president asked me to go get some.
I'll join you.
Oh, there she is.
Okudaira!
Heathcliff's stick, it...
Oh man, they broke it.
Got it! I'll be right there!
Sorry, Ikumi.
It's no big deal.
So what do you want?
Orange juice, please.
See you in a bit, Fumi.
Sure. Good luck.
Manjoume?
Yes?
Would you like something to drink too?
Um...
Sorry for having to ask you to help me.
It's okay.
So, is the person you like Sugimoto?
You too, huh?
She really is something special.
There are lots of girls who like her.
Yes, I see that.
Okay, good work, guys.
It's finally over.
Good work.
Good work!
You too!
You were awesome!
Thanks. Get home safe.
Did you hear that?
Not fair!
Here you go.
Oh, Kyouko, you're so thoughtful.
Um...
Fumi!
All third-years gather around! We've got a meeting!
The first and second-years can go home once you finish tidying up!
Okay!
This might take some time, so don't feel you have to wait for me, Fumi.
Okay.
We're starting, Sugimoto!
Sorry. I'm ready now.
Okay, start with the lines on page 75...
Fumi!
Achan.
So you're not going home with Sugimoto today?
Yeah. She said she's gonna be late.
Say, wanna join us for tea?
Ikumi is coming too.
As long as you're both okay with it.
Ikumi, can Fumi join us?
Sure, of course.
They're my girls.
I take them all over the place.
Fumi!
Hi, Mom? I'm near Kamakura station.
Yeah, with Achan and another friend.
She's so diligent, calling home to check in.
But Fumi really is a good girl.
She truly is.
Sugimoto likes her, doesn't she?
Huh?
I...
had the wrong idea all along...
Ikumi?
What's wrong?
Hey!
Sugimoto
Incoming Call
Did I wake you?
No...
It's not a big deal, but...
Uh-huh...
You didn't say you'd wait for me, so I got worried.
I'm sorry.
If you have something on your mind, tell me.
Tell me, Fumi.
I won't be able to sleep otherwise.
I talked with Ikumi Kyouko.
She said she liked you and was in tears.
I see.
Hey, Fumi.
Yes?
Do you remember your first love?
Huh?
Do you remember the first person you fell in love with?
Fumi!
Good morning.
Something good happened to you, didn't it?
Huh?
Well, Sugimoto called me yesterday.
Oh? That's great!
Yeah.
Do you remember your first love?
My... first love.
The school day is over for everyone but those in the school play and the crew.
I repeat...
Don't you feel like we're missing something?
Maybe we should add some more flowers.
Yeah, that might do it.
Look at them.
What are the elementary schoolers putting on again?
The Little Prince, wasn't it?
That girl's the Little Prince?
Yup.
The Rose?
That's her, isn't it?
So cute!
Be careful not to bump into anything.
Okay.
It's fragile.
Got it.
So they're rehearsing.
Hey, do you know where Sugimoto is?
I doubt she's here yet.
I wonder when we'll get to see her.
Well, the elementary school students do theirs first, so...
Anyway, she's not here yet!
See you later!
There's no need to worry so much.
Farewell.
Yes, farewell.
I'm fine, really, Okudaira.
As for the big animals, I'm not afraid of them.
I have my own claws.
You made up your mind to leave. Now go.
I never imagined that
two people having mutual feelings for one another
could make another person sad.
I was a fool.
I should never have run away.
I should have realized...
...the tenderness underlying her silly pretensions.
You don't want to go?
That's right.
Well, I don't want to go if you aren't going.
But you're playing the lead, Sugimoto...
You think it'll be awkward to see Kyouko?
Yes... I think it will be.
I've been seeing her all the time, though.
That's because she's been asking to see you.
I want to ask you to go out too.
Don't say that to me like that...
You feel bad for her, don't you, Fumi?
Well, whatever. I'll go by myself today.
This is impressive.
Did you make it yourself, Kyouko?
I couldn't do it by myself.
The others here helped me.
That's really great. Good work, guys.
Oh, it was nothing!
We're just doing our job!
What's the matter with you, dummy?
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Sugimoto!
Do you like sweets?
We brought you cakes.
If you'd be so kind...
Wow.
Thank you.
Since you brought them to me, how about we share?
N-No, that wasn't our intent!
Everyone fawns all over her.
I'm sure Fumi didn't want to see this.
Um, well then, we'll go get some plates and forks!
Great. Thanks.
Ikumi...
Oh, wow, Kyouko. These are homemade.
Can you stand for a second, Sugimoto?
Sorry. Please stand still.
All right.
Achan!
Want some cake, Achan?
G-Gladly!
I'm going to tack hem it.
Let me know if it's hard to move anywhere.
I'll put on a pot of tea.
Oh, thanks.
I'd normally ask Fumi, if she were here...
Come with me, Ikumi!
Huh?
H-Hey!
Achan sure is full of energy.
Look at these. They're incredible.
Look at how she has her arms around her.
Her hands look so scandalous!
Look. Isn't that amazing?
I wonder if they'll kiss on stage.
Pardon us.
What was that all about?
Okay, where's the black tea?
They make such a racket about it because they don't really like her.
But I'm different.
Fujigaya Station
Huh?
Sorry. I still have something I have to do.
Shall I wait for you?
Thanks, but it's okay.
I'm just a fan in the crowd, aren't I?
Just like those other girls.
Was that directed at me?
We're the only two people here.
You told me to just treat you like I always have, Kyouko.
Don't take what I said literally.
I was just trying to act strong.
That's just like you to say that.
You're adorable.
Like a little sister, you mean?
You really have a hard time getting over things.
But you're a good girl, so I
won't make a big deal about it.
You're cruel.
I'll be all right now.
Fumi!
What is it, Mom?
Fumi.
Sugimoto...
What is it?
Sorry, I just wanted to see your face.
Work the desk?
Yes.
At the play.
I already told the club president you'd do it.
Huh?
I figured you wouldn't come otherwise.
That's...
That's not true.
Really?
So you'll come if I ask you to?
I will.
Okay.
Um...
Hmm?
Good luck.
You too.
You aren't cold?
I'm all right.
That's a new outfit, isn't it?
It's cute.
Please don't tease me.
Aww, you shoulda told her!
I didn't have a chance.
I was just being jealous.
And that's fine! You're a lady, after all!
Anyway, you need to be really
straightforward with a person like her.
Tell her flat out you don't want other girls flirting with her!
Huh?
Isn't that a bit of a strange thing to say?
You think?
Still, I'm glad, because I thought you might end up not going to the play.
Actually, I'm really glad myself.
Let's do our best at the play tomorrow.
Yeah.
I hope it's a success.
Wuthering Heights (Part One)
While I was sleeping
like the arrival of spring
my secretly awakened love
became clear before I realized it
I leave town heading for the sound of your trembling heart
You always make me smile when you're by my side
I want to tell you one word about my love